<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Rough Draft]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Rough Draft]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/steve-abbott-author/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 01:10:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/steve-abbott-author/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 01:10:34 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Looking back]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Looking back</h1><p>There&apos;s a joke I tell every now and then. &quot;Hindsight is 20/20 and all you see is an asshole.&quot; I&apos;m not a huge fan of New Years even though my wife and friends do have a pretty fun time at our annual get together at our friend&apos;s house where they host a murder mystery.</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2018/01/0p8a6117.jpg?w=1280"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2018/01/01/looking-back/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6cad11b6-b4c5-4ff1-92d0-0f098a33af68</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 01:08:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Riding in Caceres, Spain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Riding in Caceres, Spain</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/beaf23e8-8e4f-4244-8f33-5e166212caf8.jpg">,<p>This October I was in Spain for my cousin Lucy’s wedding. After seeing a map of the area where the wedding was going to be held, I decided to rent a motorcycle instead of a car. It was the kind of decision that has both benefits and consequences for your travel. For one, you’re really restricted as to what you can bring luggage wise as whatever comes with you will have to be able to be stored on the bike. I also opted to use a supplied helmet rather than bring my own which in hindsight was a mistake. Not because the quality of the supplied helmet was lacking. It was the wrong decision because my helmet has a camera mount on it. So my usual load of thousands of images was reduced to less than twenty because I was far more focused on riding than taking pictures.</p>,<p>I’d also not considered how tired I would be after an eight hour flight followed by an the hours of negotiating Madrid to pick up my bike, transfer my gear onto the bike, find gas for the bike, negotiate how the whole fuel thing is handled in Spain (you pay at the till, not at the pump) and get out of Madrid heading South to Caceres.</p>,<p>The Bike I’d reserved was a Honda CRX700 with a decent set of Givi cases and top box. My gear fit handily inside and I’d brought some rock straps with me to strap down my folded up luggage bag across the back seat. The bike felt relatively light but a little nutless in the power department. The gear spacing felt weird too with a fairly long first gear and a ridiculously short second gear. It also had the largest horn button I’ve ever seen and there were more than a few honks from me by accident before I got my hands figured out on the bars.</p>,<p>Riding through Spain reminded me a lot of the US southern midwest except the trucks were all cab overs and generally sized a lot shorter than the standard semi rig you encounter in North America. Everybody keeps to the right except to pass which was nice and allowed me to make good time heading towards Banos de Montemayor, my destination for the day and what was going to be my place of residence for the next few days while I got acquainted with my cousin and her husband to be.</p>,<p>You don’t realize how well tuned you are to your own bike until you have to ride something else for a while. I’ve got a set of forward highway pegs that let me stretch out my legs on my Strom and I really began to miss them about two hours into my ride. I was also on a stock seat. Which to be fair, wasn’t bad but I could tell, too much of it was going to hurt me (something that was going to prove only too true later). The CRX had a couple of other minor irritants. It took me a few minutes to figure out where the gas cap was. My bike’s old school and the tank is the tank. On the CRX, the tank is just a cover for a place to store your helmet or in my case, my camera bag. The real tank was under my ass and the gas cap was under the pillion seat. When I raised the point to the rental agency, the guy said, I looked like I knew what I was about, so he wasn’t worried about it. Fair cop to him I guess. Still, no hand guards or grip heaters and a tiny windshield. All the joys of riding a basically naked bike.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a2723e46-ecb9-4108-aa29-cf2bd39f71aa.jpg">,<p>I had opted for a GPS from the rental company and they were able to provide me with a very basic Garmin, stuck to my tank with a suction cup and further secured with some wire, “Just in case.” A far cry from my Zumo 600 but good enough to get me where I needed to be.</p>,<p>Banos De Montemayor lay at the bottom of a valley. The town had buildings with capstones dating from 1792 and you got the feeling it had been there a while. It’s very much the sort of place you walk around. My lodgings were in the center of the town, literally round the corner from where my cousin and her friends were having an afternoon drink at one of the numerous cantinas.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a12e7d10-9b1b-400b-9f61-63c480925081.jpg">,<p>The streets were really narrow and fairly steep. Even on the motorcycle, parking was… interesting and scarce. Scarce enough I ended up storing the bike in a shed for three days and hoofing it everywhere.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/4a185a17-9333-4e85-af42-c37731406490.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/fbde874f-6524-407e-91ae-927b32be4658.jpg">,<p>More to come…</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/steve-abbott-author/riding-in-caceres-spain/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">542b9353-107a-4920-9aca-9b9df3d5055b</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 01:49:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Art of Forgetting - Part 5]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Art of Forgetting - Part 5</h1><p>Welcome back. Sorry this is taking so long to post up. Life is what happens when you&apos;re making other plans. Still a bit stiff from our ride out from Bamfield to Port Alberni, we stopped for some Subway (my go to for road food) before gassing up the bikes and deciding we&apos;d hit up our...</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2017/08/dsc06068.jpg?w=1280"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2017/08/13/the-art-of-forgetting-part-5/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a4c345f7-867a-42fb-90e2-792422904471</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 14:51:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Canso]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Canso</h1><p>Today I finally got to fly in the Canadian Warplane Heritage Museum&apos;s PBY 5A Canso. I&apos;ve been waiting for her to become available for flights for a few years now. I&apos;ve always loved the PBY 5A and have dreamed about flying in one for years. Weather delayed my flight a bit as a few rain...</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2017/08/0p8a2696.jpg?w=1280"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2017/08/05/canso/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">54dcb8d8-649a-416a-a618-a01ef7399f15</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 14:51:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Art of Forgetting - Part 4]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Art of Forgetting - Part 4</h1><p>By this point in my trip log, you&apos;re probably wondering why I&apos;ve labelled this, &quot;The art of forgetting.&quot; Well as any of you who&apos;ve been following me for any amount of time, you know I&apos;m originally from BC. The Fraser Valley to be exact. After my family emigrated to Canada we stayed in Vancouver for...</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/dsc05338.jpg?w=1280"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2017/07/22/the-art-of-forgetting-part-4/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d7a85383-917c-48b6-8f75-ecd26e41744f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 14:51:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Art of Forgetting - Part 3]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Art of Forgetting - Part 3</h1><p>I don&apos;t have any shots coming out of Lake Cowichan but we were just down the road from the local Timmies so we got some hot tea in me and some coffee in Mark and after a quick about face, som...</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/dsc04902.jpg?w=1280"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2017/07/16/the-art-of-forgetting-part-3/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c7ca3350-755f-414c-be0d-21628a1b122e</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 14:51:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The art of Forgetting - Part 2]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The art of Forgetting - Part 2</h1><p>If Utah and Colorado were all about the heat, Vancouver Island was going to be about water. As you can see in the picture above, the concrete is wet as are the bikes. Trouble is at this point it&apos;s all holding off. So the choice was made to leave the rain gear off and risk...</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/dsc04280.jpg?w=1280"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2017/07/02/the-art-of-forgetting-part-2/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eebd321e-0fbb-4330-9d17-0085bcd6550a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 14:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The art of forgetting - part 1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The art of forgetting - part 1</h1><p>It&apos;s been a month since I&apos;ve posted anything up on the blog and for that I apologize. Things have been a bit hectic around here before, during and after my return from our trip out to the west coast. Some of which I&apos;m happy to talk about and others (not so much) but we&apos;ll get...</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2017/07/dazpnuoxuaajcoz.jpg?w=1280"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2017/07/01/the-art-of-forgetting-part-1/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e3366bb5-ca2e-49a9-96c1-988f0c87a674</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 14:51:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Another Step]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Another Step</h1><p>Good news! I&apos;m in the initial stages of turning Devil&apos;s Gambit into an audio book through Findaway Voices. I&apos;ve been looking to do this for some time now but the Amazon ACX system was defeating me at every turn due to my Canadian address. The process is not cheap but the chance to expand my...</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2014/11/42186773ed09b964d4ab807f708065eb3a17cd0b08d1815d-original.jpg?w=306&h=488"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2016/11/19/another-step/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7deac47c-d2de-4fff-88c1-b2048eeb681f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 15:42:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brampton Airport Open House 2016]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Brampton Airport Open House 2016</h1><p>I missed last year&apos;s open house because of work. It&apos;s a great day out with vintage cars, bikes and aircraft. I switched over to my Sigma 150mm-500m f4.5 as they were starting to get aircraft in position to fly. I swapped lenses and went back to the Twist 60.</p><img src="https://sabot03196.files.wordpress.com/2016/09/img_3991-xl.jpg?w=1280"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://sabot03196.wordpress.com/2016/09/11/brampton-airport-open-house-2016/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">59dbaaa6-6e33-4bf6-b97f-0efe4944b687</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 00:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>